{
    "results": [
        {
            "id": 0,
            "question": "What keyword is used to define a constant in Swift?",
            "correct_answer": "var",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "const",
                "let",
                "const var"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "How large is an Int?",
            "correct_Answer": "64 bits",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "16 bits",
                "32 bits",
                "It depends on the platform"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "Structures can't:",
            "correct_Answer": "Conform to protocols to provide standard functionality of a certain kind",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Define properties to store values",
                "Define initializers to set up their initial state",
                "Inherit the characteristics of another structure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What is the type and value of str in the following expression?",
            "correct_Answer": "Type: String, Value: \"12.0\"",
            "incorrect_answers": [                "Type: String?, Value: \"12.0\"",
                "Type: String, Value: \"12\"",
                "Type: String?, Value: nil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "What operator takes two numbers, and returns a boolean?",
            "correct_Answer": "all of the above",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "<",
                ">",
                "==",
                "!=",
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "What does the following code output?",
            "correct_Answer": "3",
            "answeincorrect_answersrs": [
                "0",
                "6",
                "10"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "What is the following function's return type?",
            "correct_Answer": "Bool",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "String",
                "Int",
                "It doesn't have a return type"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "Structures can't:",
            "correct_Answer": "Conform to protocols to provide standard functionality of a certain kind",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Define properties to store values",
                "Define initializers to set up their initial state",
                "Inherit the characteristics of another structure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Why might you throw an error?",
            "correct_Answer": "The code has become too complicated to continue writing",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The code has become too easy",
                "Something unexpected happened and the normal flow of execution can't continue",
                "To pass data to a caller method"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "How can you deal with an error?",
            "correct_Answer": "By informing the user of the failure",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "By correcting the problem",
                "By trying an alternative approach",
                "All of the above"
            ]
        }
    ]
}
